{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "Which of the following should you do to restrict access to company files and devices?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Update your software once a year.",
		                "Share passwords only with colleagues you trust.",
		                "Access information via an open Wi-Fi network.",
		                "Use multi-factor authentication."
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which of this is the strongest password",
		            "content" : [
		                "abcd1234",
		                "xPh1230252rpfrkfwefoi3or0",
		                "a@pQr2591v!63",
		                "johnnydoe"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "You get a supicious email with a link, you should",
		            "content" : [
		                "Open it immediately ",
		                "Open the link in incognito",
		                "Report the link to the company IT security",
		                "Forward it to coworker"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "By opening malicious emails and pop-ups you are exposing the company to and providing personal information",
		            "content" : [
		                "Phishing",
		                "Ransomware Attacks",
		                "Identity theft",
		                "All of these"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 3
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "How should you manage your passwords",
		            "content" : [
		                "By remembering all of them",
		                "Writing down in a notebook",
		                "Using encryption based password manager",
		                "Keeping it the same everywhere"
		            ],
		            "correct" : 2
		        },
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Use home wifi only",
				        "Use personal VPN like NordVPN",
				        "Connect through public",
					"Use company's private VPN"
				    ],
				    "question": "When you are working from home, you should"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 2,
				    "content": [
				        "Antivirus Software",
"Company IT Security team", "Well setup firewall", "Police and Government"
				    ],
				    "question": "What is the first line of defence against cyberattacks?"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 1,
				    "content": [
				        "Paying the money when it happens",
"Data backup", "Strong antivirus software", "Using secured VPN"
				    ],
				    "question": "What is the best defence against ransomware attack"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 2,
				    "content": [
				        "Can be ignored",
				        "Can be delayed",
				        "Should be done immediately when released",
				        "Should be done in batches"
				    ],
				    "question": "Software updates"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 1,
				    "content": [
				        "Leave the laptop on your desk unlocked and logged in",
				        "Log out and if possible, physically lock the device",
				        "Take it with you",
				        "Leave it with a colleague"
				    ],
				    "question": "When going out for a coffee, you should"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Open or run it immediately",
				        "Delete it",
				        "Open it in a virtual environment",
				        "Get it scanned with antivirus software"
				    ],
				    "question": "After downloading an email attachment, you should"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Share them",
				        "Share them after encrypting them",
				        "Report the colleague",
				        "Politely decline"
				    ],
				    "question": "Your colleague needs to access some information quickly and is asking for your credentials"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 1,
				    "content": [
				        "Access company work from cybercafe",
				        "Consult with your boss and the IT security department",
				        "Don't do the work",
				        "Access company work from spouse's laptop"
				    ],
				    "question": "You are on holiday but need to do some work urgently and don't have office laptop with you"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 0,
				    "content": [
				        "93%",
				        "25%",
				        "100%",
				        "50%"
				    ],
				    "question": "What percentage of employees engage in atleast some poor data security practice?"
				},
				{
				    "correct": 3,
				    "content": [
				        "Get you fired",
				        "Cause huge loss to the organization",
				        "Can harm you",
				        "All of these"
				    ],
				    "question": "Not following company security policies and training can"
				}
		    ]
		
		}
	]
}
